♪ Hey, good lookin'
Whatcha got cookin' ♪
♪ Hows about cookin'
Something up with me ♪
♪ Hey, sweet baby
Don't you think maybe ♪
♪ We could find us
A brand new recipe ♪
♪ I got a hot rod Ford
And a two dollar bill ♪
♪ And I know a place
Right over the hill ♪
♪ Where... ♪
I forget it.
Bones, I forgot it.
♪ Hey, good lookin' ♪
♪ Whatcha got cookin' ♪
♪ Hows about cookin'
Something up for me ♪
Yeehaw!
I didn't really want to sing
that song, anyhow, actually.
But I got another one
here I'd like to sing.
I'd like to sing a song
and I'd like to dedicate it
to my beautiful wife,
Kitty Carroll, right here.
Okay.
Ain't she something?
Stand back.
♪ I tried so hard
My dear to show ♪
♪ That you're my every dream ♪
♪ Yet you're afraid
Each thing thing I do ♪
♪ Is just some evil scheme ♪
♪ A memory from
Your lonesome past ♪
♪ Keeps us so far a-apart ♪
♪ Why can't I free
Your doubtful mind ♪
♪ And melt Your
cold cold heart ♪
♪ Another love before my time
Made your heart sad and blue ♪
♪ And so my heart
Is payin' now ♪
♪ For things I did not do ♪
♪ In anger unkind
words Are said ♪
♪ That make The
teardrops start ♪
♪ Why can't I free
Your doubtful mind ♪
♪ And melt Your
cold cold heart ♪
See if I ever dedicate
another song to you.
Hey, but it don't matter,
'cause I'll tell ya, Jimmy
Legrand don't get mad.
He just gets even.
Kitty?
Kitty!
Listen to me, please.
Just what are you doing?
I'm not talking to you.
Yes, you are.
I'm not taking any
more notes from you.
I want to know what's wrong
and I want to know right now.
You're drunk.
That's what's wrong.
Aw. I told you, Jim.
I said if you didn't stop
drinking or raising hell,
then I was going to
walk out on you for good,
and that's exactly
what's going on right now.
Look, you can't do
this. This tour is not over.
We got five more bookings.
You leave and you
ain't never coming back.
What in sam hill's
going on, Jimmy?
Now, Jimmy, just wait. Jimmy!
Tom, get 'em both
back on the stage.
Have 'em do... No... Just have
him tell every story he knows.
Luann. Luann,
she is you're sister.
You gotta talk to her.
There ain't nothing
to talk about.
She's had it and it's over.
All of it.
Listen, you can't do this.
Just think what
it'll do to Jimmy.
You're worried about Jimmy,
huh? Don't make me laugh.
All you're worried about
is losing your meal ticket.
Oh, yeah. You just let him drink
and let him make
an ass out of himself
so you can steal from him.
You're nothing but parasites
hanging on and sucking him dry.
Hey, lady. You're
way out of line!
You don't give a hoot what
happens to Jimmy or Kitty,
and if your tour shuts
down, it'll serve you right.
Oh, my God.
It's Kitty Carroll.
No. It's Luann, her sister.
I think she's dead.
Somebody call the police!
Okay. Now, if I can
just get this clear...
Careful. Yep.
Here we go. Wait. Wait.
Yeah. Okay. You got it?
I think so. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
It's clear. Ahh.
Hey. Ha-ha-ha. Oh.
What do you think?
Oh, it's just gorgeous.
The face and
the... It's beautiful.
Look at that wood. Ooh.
Look at that workmanship.
The inlay. Mm-hm
This wonderful little
window. Oh, yes. Beautiful.
It's got to be 100
years old. Oh, yes.
Maybe more. Oh, maybe more. Yes.
How long do you
think it'll take to fix it?
Well, I've got a guy
that owes me a favor.
I expect he can get right on it.
I hear there's this little
old man over in Athens
who fixes antique
clocks for a living.
Well, yeah. Of course, this
guy that owes me the favor,
he could probably save you some:
You sure he can fix it?
Oh, yes. He can fix anything.
Okay. All right.
Coffee?
I'll see you at dinner.
Oh, okay. Okay.
L-Let's try Alfredo's, huh?
Okay. Okay. Okay Ha-ha-ha. Bye.
Bye.
There's a beauty.
That's a beauty.
This... Go in, then.
There you are.
Yeah.
Damn.
This is Ben Matlock.
Actually, it's my
answering machine,
because I'm not here right now.
But if you leave your
name and number
at the sound of the
beep, I'll call you back.
That's a promise.
Hi. Ben. It's Michelle.
Oh, Michelle. It's Sunday.
I know it's Sunday,
but I thought maybe,
just maybe, you'd be home.
I'm not home.
Sorry you're not home,
because the service
just called me to say that a
woman named Kitty Carroll
wants to talk to you.
Country singer?
She's a country-western
singer or something.
Anyway, I'll just say
I couldn't reach you.
No. No, wait. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Hold it. Wait. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait... Hello?
Why, Ben. What a surprise.
Uh, hey, listen, Michelle.
Tell, uh, Kitty Carroll that
I'd be delighted to meet her.
Where?
She'll be at the
office in half an hour.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Well, uh...
Luann, she didn't have
an enemy in the world,
but she was driving
my car and it was...
We always dressed alike.
It was 3 in the morning
and the parking lot
wasn't very well lit.
The police think whoever
was driving that car
was trying to kill you.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's one of the
reasons they arrested Jimmy.
Why would your
husband want to kill you?
Well, I made him
very angry last night.
I-I-I walked off the stage
in the middle of the show
and I told him that it
was finished between us.
What brought that about?
Jimmy's always
been kind of wild, see,
and, uh, when we... When we
got married about three years ago,
h-he promised me
that he would change,
and... And he did for a while.
He... He stopped drinking
and, uh, he stopped
going to dives.
Then about, uh, five months
ago, when we started this tour,
he kinda started going downhill.
He was drinking and picking
fights with everybody and...
Smashing up cars.
He's been in jail twice.
I read about that. I was
hoping it was just something
some press agent had made
up to hike the ticket sales.
You sound like a fan.
Well, you could say.
He has all your
husband's records.
Go ahead.
Things just went from bad
to worse and nothing I said...
I-It j-just didn't seem
to make any difference.
And then when we
came into town last night,
Luann and I went
to this other motel
instead of staying
at the Emerald
where everybody else was.
Then I sent Jimmy a
message and I told him
that if he didn't shape
up once and for all,
then I was going to file
for divorce and I meant it.
What'd he do?
He showed up drunk,
so I walked off the stage
and out of his life.
You think your husband
was trying to kill you?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
I can't remember anything,
but I'd never hurt Kitty,
drunk or sober.
I don't care what kind
of fool thing I was in.
I couldn't have killed Luann.
Do you remember driving
your car after the concert?
Um. Larry drove.
I was, uh, pretty loaded,
so he took everybody over
to this country music place
we always hang out in when
we're here. The Ramblers.
After that, my memory
gets a little fuzzy.
Who's everybody?
Um, well, everybody would be
uh, Larry Thorpe,
that's my manager,
and Lloyd Wylie.
The drummer.
Uh-huh.
And Bones, Bones Jennings.
The fiddle player.
Yeah.
When did you
leave, uh, Ramblers?
I... I don't remember.
I must have passed out.
So you don't know
who drove from the club
back to the motel
where you were staying?
Well, probably Larry.
Uh, Bones and Wylie
usually get drunker than I do,
but Larry, he likes
to stay in control.
He's afraid somebody's gonna
steal his money or something.
Hm. Yeah.
Well, uh, the arraignment
will probably be
sometime this afternoon.
My associate's finding out
where and when, and, uh,
if we can arrange bail,
maybe we can get you
out of here by tonight.
Kitty thinks I did
it, doesn't she?
Right now she's not sure.
I can't say I blame her.
Boy, I sure could
use a drink right now.
I'm gonna tell you something.
If we get you out of this, you
gonna have to get straight.
You just argue diminished
capacity all you want.
Jimmy Legrand had a
high tolerance for alcohol.
He can drink a lot,
and you don't know
that he didn't drive his
car to and from the scene
and specifically choose his
victim. You don't know that.
This man was
able to form intent.
He just mistook
her sister for her.
He said he didn't.
He said he didn't, and
there are no witnesses
who can place him
behind that wheel.
A, pieces of the victim's
dress were found entangled
in the crumbled front
end of your client's car.
B, your client's fingerprints
were found all over
it's steering wheel.
And C, your client
was found in said car
just four hours
after the murder.
But that doesn't prove
that he was driving the car
at the time of the murder,
and what makes you
so sure it was murder
and not an accident?
Ben, he's made
threats all over town.
I'll be surprised
if Judge Cooksey
even grants bail.
The man is not a
hardened criminal.
Can we have... I'll
just have water, please.
Three years in prison
for assault with
a deadly weapon?
It was a fight in a barroom.
Oh. He's been arrested
twice in the last two months.
Well...
This kind of behavior is
willful and self-centered
and he's a menace to society.
Uh, well, could...
Thank you. Thank you.
Could... Could we just
stop here for a minute?
I want to make a
statement. Mm-hm.
Now, I'm fond of you
in many ways. I know.
In... In many ways,
I'm crazy about you.
That doesn't change
the fact that the man...
L-Let me go ahead.
Let me go ahead here.
Uh. In many ways, we
have a different point of view.
You're a prosecuting attorney.
You think like a prosecuting
attorney and you should.
I'm a criminal lawyer.
I-I'm a defense attorney
and I think like one.
Now, I know that Jimmy
Legrand is not a wonderful person.
If you're truthful, he's
a menace to society.
He's not wonderful. Heh-heh.
He has a long ways
to go to be nice.
Now, I know there's a lot
of circumstantial
evidence against him,
but I have agreed to defend him,
and the man has written
some fine country songs:
"Down the Dusty Road,"
"Red Rosy Sunset."
So many wonderful and,
to me, meaningful songs.
And I have to believe that
somewhere in his deep recesses,
there is some
good, some decency.
Besides, I don't
think he did it.
I was just trying to point
out what you're getting into.
I never said it was
gonna be easy.
Oh, well, that's
an understatement.
Well, the good part
is I'm just his lawyer.
I-I'm not his friend.
I'll work for him,
do the best I can.
The saints be saved,
he doesn't live with me.
That isn't quite true.
I was afraid Judge Cooksey
was going to deny bail,
so I made a little speech
about your great regard
for Jimmy and his music,
and Judge Cooksey says
since you think so highly of him,
his quote was:
"You can have him."
He ordered him to
stay at your house
for the duration of the trial.
You're kidding.
Hey, old buddy.
I understand we're
gonna be roomies.
I'll take that.
I go nuts hanging
around that motel.
Without Kitty, my car,
reporters bugging
me all the time,
I think me staying with
you is about the best idea
I've heard in a long time.
Well, that's about
it. This is the kitchen.
D-Does Kitty know I'm here?
Yeah. I mentioned it to her.
I'm afraid she, uh,
doesn't want to see you.
Do you have any
beer in this place?
Now, listen.
Yeah, that's right. I
know. I'm off it. Okay.
What you got there?
Um... It's mine. Huh.
It's not much.
Not much?
It's a sweetheart.
You know, if whoever
ran down Luann
was really after Kitty,
he might still be after her.
I talked her into hiring
a bodyguard for awhile,
but I sure do wish I knew
who might be after her.
I just don't know.
All the guys in
the band loved her.
Please, uh, help yourself.
Thank you.
Ahem. So you've been staying
here ever since you
arrived in Atlanta?
Um-hm. I figured if Jimmy
didn't know where I was,
he'd take the ultimatum
of my note seriously.
Why'd you send a note?
Why didn't you
tell him in person?
To be perfectly
honest, Mr. Matlock,
I was afraid of how he'd react.
Do you have any idea
what Luann was doing
in the parking lot of the
Emerald Motel that night?
I vaguely remember
hearing the phone ring, but...
Any men in her life?
Not really.
Luann had real high standards
and men had a real
tough time living up to 'em.
In fact, she was
constantly fighting them off.
Have you met Lloyd Wylie?
Yeah.
Well, about a month
ago, Lloyd Wylie...
He's the drummer
on tour with us.
Well, he came on
real strong to Luann
and, uh, she said
thanks but no thanks
as nicely as possible,
but things were
tense for awhile.
You know, real tense.
Nah. That's just Lloyd.
He likes to think
he's irresistible.
Why was Luann driving
your car that night?
I have no idea.
Hers is still parked outside.
What's going on?
Hey, Ben. Where
ya been all this time?
We're having us a party here.
All right, all right.
Folks. Hey, folks.
The party's over. I need
everybody to go home.
Come on, get outta here.
Hey, come on. I'm just
trying to make myself
a few new friends
here, that's all.
Get outta here!
Hey, Jim, you look like hell.
Why don't you get some sleep?
Get outta here!
Get outtta here! Go on! Get out!
Let's hit the road. Woo!
Come on.
Jimmy?
Hey.
We're going to
have a talk, mister.
All right. All right.
All right. Yep.
All right. Drink this.
Huh?
Come on. Drink this.
Take it.
Oh, my Lord.
Now, you listen.
You're here because the
judge ordered you to be here.
I'm defending you
on a murder charge.
It could be that
I'm the only thing
between you and
a lot of hard time.
So from now on, you're
going to do exactly as I say.
No partying, no drinking.
If I get you out of this
and you want to ruin
your life after the trial,
that's fine with me,
but I'll be damned if
you're going to do it
while you're in my
house. You got that?
Uh...
Larry, this is a valid
contract. You signed it.
I know it is, but Bones, we just
don't have any money coming in.
You guaranteed us
our salary whether...
Whether Jimmy
could perform or not.
I can't pay it if I don't
have any money.
You guaranteed to pay us if
Jimmy could perform or not.
I'd pay it out of
my own pocket...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy, Lloyd.
I'll buy you a drink. Come on.
Come on. buddy.
Your drummer's got a bad temper.
He accused me
of cheating on him.
Hell, I can't pay out salaries.
Not with us stuck out here,
but Lloyd, he thinks
I'm holding out on him.
What did Luann Carroll think?
A couple of stagehands
heard what went on
backstage that night.
That Luann accused you
of stealing from Jimmy.
Whoa, whoa. Wait a minute.
Now, there was a bunch
of us standing back there.
She wasn't talking to me.
She meant somebody else.
Who?
I don't know.
Listen, you want to
take a look at my books?
Be my guest.
Maybe you can tell
me how I'm supposed
to pay salaries out
of a shut down tour.
I'm sure you're doing
the best you can.
Well, there. There, see?
Anybody can play the drums.
I'll tell you what.
Come over to my house tonight,
I'll give you a nice,
long private lesson.
Hey, bartend.
Mr. Wylie, Bones. Howdy.
I talked to the police.
Your alibi's good.
That little lady
corroborated your story
about spending
the night with you.
Hi.
Mm.
You have a way with
women, don't you?
I mean that assault
case over in Charlotte.
That woman you beat up.
The one who withdrew the
charges almost immediately.
That's what I mean when I
say you have a way with women.
It always seems to
work in your best interest.
Are you saying I got
that woman to lie?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm just saying you have
a way of handling women.
That wasn't quite the case with
Luann Carroll, though, was it?
She was the one who
got away, wasn't she?
Or did she?
You like to live dangerously,
don't you, mister?
Most people won't hit a man
with my color hair in public.
I hear Luann accused some
people of stealing from Jimmy.
Any idea why she'd do that?
Jimmy'd give most of
us the shirt off his back
if we'd asked for it.
That's not how Luann thought.
In her mind, we were
stealing the shirt off his back.
Just her way of
looking at the world.
She may have been right.
You know, Bones,
some people are
under the impression
that you have been
Jimmy's whipping boy.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, it could mean that
you were a good friend
when he needed one.
Or it could mean
you resented him,
it's hard to say.
I resent you.
Hey, Bones.
See ya, son.
Can I get you something, mister?
No, I'm fine.
I see you know Jimmy
Legrand's fiddle player.
That mean you know Jimmy?
Oh, oh, yeah.
Served him hundreds of times.
It's his favorite hangout
every time he's in Atlanta.
In fact, he was in here
the night after
his last concert.
Hm. The night that, uh,
Luann Carroll
got herself killed.
Uh... I'm, uh,
Jimmy's lawyer, Mr...?
My name's, uh, Fitzsimmons.
Well, I understand that
Jimmy was pretty drunk
when he left here that night.
Well, uh... No, sir.
I mean, uh, I don't let none
of my customers
leave here drunk.
I mean, that's the law.
Oh, well, I... I... I
didn't mean that...
Uh, excuse me, will you?
I got a customer down here.
Yeah, what can I get for you?
Damn it, Jimmy.
I'm not drunk, just awkward.
What are you doing?
I was looking for a pot.
I promised to stop
drinking, not eating.
How's ham hocks
and black-eyed peas
sound to you?
Right.
Mm. Delicious.
Poor folk food.
Yeah.
Want some onions?
Mm-hm.
Okay.
Did you see Kitty today?
Yeah. How's she doing?
She's doing fine.
She's afraid of you now.
Seems to think you
got a bad temper.
That's the reason
she sent you that note
instead of having it
out with you in person.
Well, I'm not easy.
No idea.
See, Kitty's the first woman
who ever believed in me.
And I guess I just wasn't
ready to handle that.
Well, I got to tell
you one thing,
if you can't make it with her,
I don't know who you're
going to make it with.
Yeah.
So what'd you do
when you got the note?
Just what anybody else would do.
I read it, put it down.
And, uh, threw a
chair out the window.
Well, it was either that or
kick the hell out of Bones.
He was the one who
brought me the note.
Say,
how about you take
a note to her from me?
How about that?
Well... Hey.
Yeah, I've been
working on it a little.
Oh, it don't keep no good time.
Yeah.
Keeps good rhythm,
though, don't it?
Oh, Julie's gonna be so mad.
Lieutenant Peters has
testified that when he found
Mr. Legrand in the car
that struck and
killed Luann Carroll,
he appeared to be intoxicated.
Now, did you serve Mr. Legrand
any alcohol that night?
Yes, ma'am, I did.
Did you see him leave
your establishment?
Yea, ma'am, he left
with some friends.
And in your opinion,
was he intoxicated when he left?
Well, he, uh... He...
He sure looked drunk.
Mr. Fitzsimmons, you look like
you're holding back something.
Just tell us, under
oath, in this courtroom:
was he intoxicated?
Now, look, if you're asking
me to make Jimmy Legrand
out to be some sort of liar...
Answer the question, please.
Well, I... I'd say he
looked drunk because, well,
I'd... I'd been serving him
watered-down
drinks all night long.
No, ma'am, I don't see how
he could have been drunk.
What do you mean,
"watered-down drinks?"
Well, I mean drinks with
hardly any booze in them.
Bones, uh... Mr. Jennings
had told me to.
He... He said that he
was worried about Jimmy,
something to do
with his wife, so I...
I did like he said
and I served him mostly
mixer all night long.
No, ma'am, I...
I don't see how in the world
he could have been drunk.
In other words,
you think Mr. Legrand
was pretending to be drunk.
Objection.
Cause for speculation.
Sustained.
No further questions.
Cross-examine?
I have no questions, Your Honor.
This court is
adjourned for the day.
We'll reconvene at 9
a.m. tomorrow morning.
I was drunk that night.
I swear it. I was drunk.
I know.
I think I know who did it.
Well, afternoon.
I'm looking for,
uh, Molly Parnell.
Oh, that's me.
Oh, you must be Mr. Matlock.
Hi. This is Tyler Hudson.
Pleased to meet you. A pleasure.
Oh, uh, here are
the telephone records
and I paper clipped the
date you were interested in.
Oh, good. Thank you, ma'am.
Would you look at that?
Wow.
You mean... Do all of
these stars stay here?
You bet. Like Jimmy.
He and his tour have been
coming here for four years now,
every time they play Atlanta.
Wow.
That must be good for business
to be able to lay claim
on something like that.
Better than all the
advertising in the world.
Well, what is it you give
that other motels don't?
Low rates?
Well, they're reasonable.
Complimentary cocktails?
Are you kidding? I'd be
out of business in a day.
It must be something.
Uh, free room service
with X-rated movies?
Mr. Matlock, I thought
you were smarter than that.
Actually, I, uh...
I think you may
be able to help me.
How's that?
I think you may be
able to help me find
the person who
killed Luann Carroll.
We're gonna have
to subpoena this.
I found what we're looking for.
Thank you.
Hold it!
Mr. Legrand is as innocent
today as he was yesterday.
That's all.
I got your note.
Are you okay?
I subpoenaed everything
but the kitchen sink.
Good.
I missed you so much.
I guess, if the truth be told,
you've known Jimmy Legrand
longer than
anybody in this room.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
Him and me go back a long way.
And you've known Kitty
Carroll a long time too.
Since before they were married.
So I guess that's why
Kitty asked you
to pick up that note
and take it to Jimmy,
'cause you're old friends.
Most likely.
Did she ask you
to keep the motel
where she and her sister
were staying a secret?
I didn't tell a soul.
So, if... If Mrs.
Carroll were to testify
that she told no one else where
she and Luann were staying,
then you were the only other
member of the company to know.
Isn't that right?
I guess so.
Did you place a
call from your room
at the Emerald Motel
at exactly 2:20 a.m.
the morning Luann was killed?
No, sir.
Now, are you sure?
I subpoenaed...
your motel phone records.
Now, before I enter
this into evidence,
maybe you wanna
reconsider your testimony.
Maybe I did.
I... I can't remember.
That's all right.
You don't have to.
A call was put through
to Luann's room at exactly
2:20 a.m. that same morning.
I subpoenaed their records too.
Now, since you were the only one
who knew where
they were staying,
isn't it logical that you're
the one who made that call?
Shoot, I couldn't have done it.
I couldn't even see
the phone that night,
let alone dial it.
I was too damn drunk.
Ask Larry Thorpe.
Ask any of them.
Uh, Mr. Fitzsimmons,
the bartender,
has testified that he
did serve watered drinks,
but he didn't say,
because he couldn't,
who actually drank those
watered down drinks.
It was you, wasn't it?
No. Jimmy got 'em.
Jimmy got 'em, but
Jimmy didn't drink 'em.
You made sure that Jimmy
drank your drinks, didn't you,
so all you had to
do was act drunk
when you left The Ramblers? No.
No. That's not right.
Are you sure you didn't call
Luann's room that morning
and ask her to meet
you in your parking lot?
No, sir.
Are you sure that you didn't
get in that car beside Jimmy,
who'd long since passed out,
and use it to run
down Luann Carroll?
Well, that's crazy.
Why would I...?
Why would I kill Luann?
Kickbacks.
Oh, no.
Luann found out
about those kickbacks
you'd been getting from the
motels all over the country
where Jimmy and his
band and his entourage stay
when they're on tour.
No, Larry makes all
the hotel reservations.
How am I gonna get a kickback?
'Cause you're the one
who goes in at leaving time
and tells the manager
that he or she better cross
your palm with some cash
if they want Jimmy's
business again.
That's got to mean
in the last six years...
That means you've been
knocking down $3-400,000.
Luann found out about it
when she and Kitty changed
accommodations, didn't she?
She threatened to
tell Jimmy, didn't she?
So you killed her.
I never did.
Only problem...
Only problem was,
in using Jimmy's
car to murder Luann,
you knocked a big
hole in the radiator
so it wouldn't hold water.
And in order to try
to make it out of town,
according to plan,
with Jimmy in the car,
you had to stop somewhere
to get some water
to put in that
radiator very carefully,
hoping no one would see you.
Bones,
what if I told you
someone did see you?
Okay. What the hell?
I didn't know who she was
gonna tell about the money,
or if she was gonna
tell, or when, or nothing.
It was driving me crazy.
So at night when Kitty
walked off the stage,
everything sort
of fell into place.
So I fixed Luann's car so
that she'd have to take Kitty's,
called her, and...
shoot, you know the rest.
Everybody loves you, Jim.
No jury would
have convicted you.
Uh, Your Honor?
Move to dismiss.
The People join in the motion.
This case is dismissed.
Court is adjourned.
Congratulations.
How did you do that?
Do what?
Pick up that witness.
Michelle, it was
3 in the morning.
How could you possibly find
somebody who saw something?
I didn't.
Wait a minute. Ben,
you said... No, no.
I didn't say there
was a witness.
I said what if there
were a witness?
You just dragged
somebody off the street?
Well, not off the street.
He's an old friend
of Ben's from Athens.
Fixes antique clocks.
♪ Come sit by my side ♪
♪ Little darling ♪
♪ Come lay your cool
hand On my brow ♪
♪ Promise me that
You will never ♪
♪ Be nobody's darling But mine ♪
♪ You're sweet as the
flowers In springtime ♪
♪ You're pure as
the dew On the rose ♪
♪ Rather be somebody's darling ♪
♪ Than a poor boy
That nobody knows ♪
Honey?
I know I've never been much,
but I promise you:
from now on, whatever
it takes, I will be.
I know you will.
I hope.
♪ Promise me
That you will never ♪
♪ Be nobody's Darling but mine ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net